It’s like I’m falling apart
Too fast to realize
The damage is done
Don’t speak so soon I
Know I  already won
No questions left now
Could you please step aside
I’m done wasting my time
I’m too fucked up
I stay lost in my head
You said that we’re not done
Yet I’m better off dead
It’s all too much
I can’t stomach this debt
But I know
I know that you realize
That I can’t take back
All the moments we spent
You’ll stay stuck in my mind
And I’ll cover the rent
Just know that I’m here
For whatever comes next
Cause you won’t
No you won’t let me burn out now
Don’t waste your time on me
I know that I’m empty
Please don’t think any less of me
Now you’ve seen all I could be
I know it looks pretty
You know, you just want the best from me
I’m too fucked up
I stay lost in my head
You said that we’re not done
Yet I’m better off dead
It’s all too much
I can’t stomach this debt
But I know
I know that you realize
That I can’t take back
All the moments we spent
You’ll stay stuck in my mind
And I’ll cover the rent
Just know that I’m here
For whatever comes next
Cause you won’t
No you won’t let me burn out now
I’m falling apart too fast
Just scared of the way that my mind won’t rest
And I know I’m stuck all inside my head
But I don’t feel safe no, no I don’t feel safe cause
I’m falling apart too fast
Scared of you and I know that’s bad
Always wanted just what we have
Cause I wanna feel safe here, I wanna feel safer